https://www.schultheisautomation.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Schultheis Automation Control Systems
About UsCompany HistoryCareersPressAutomationServicesIndustriesProjectsTraining and SeminarsI.T. ServicesComputers and AccessoriesNetworking and ServersCameras and SecurityTraining and Seminars – I.T.SafetyContact
Select Page Privacy PolicySchultheisautomation.com provides this Privacy Policy to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at https://www.schultheisautomation.com/.By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to our Privacy Policy.Information we useOur primary goals in collecting personally identifiable information are to provide you with the product and services made available through the Site, including, but not limited, to the Service, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.Contact InformationIn addition, we may use contact information to provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications from us, please un-follow us.CookiesLike many websites, we also use “cookies” to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information.You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.Links to Other WebsitesOur Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.Changes to this PolicyThis Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.If you have other questions please let us know.
Search for:
I.T. SERVICESSales and Support for Desktops, Laptops, Servers, Networks, Printers and Security Cameras. We work at your site, or at our location in Jones Mills, PA.Follow Us
Facebook
Google+
Twitter Copyright 2020 Schultheisautomation.comContactSafetyTerms of ServicePrivacy Policy
